expotv.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | gen.video

This policy applies to your use of all site and services owned or operated by Expo Communications, Inc. who owns and operates gen.video (“gen.video,” “we,” “us” and “our,” as applicable), including www.gen.video and any other site that we may own or operate currently or in the future (collectively, the “Sites”). This policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites to which any of the Sites only link. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Sites. This privacy policy applies only to data gathered on the Sites and does not apply to any offline point of contact between EXPO gen.video and consumers.

_This privacy policy was updated on June 24, 2015._

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

* * *

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Since any changes will be posted on this page, we encourage you to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Sites following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

### Your IP Address

* * *

Each time you visit the Sites, our Web server automatically collects your IP address and the Web page from which you came. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Sites, and to better serve you while visiting the Sites.

### Cookies and Software

* * *

The Sites use cookies to keep track of your activity on the Sites and enhance your experience on the Sites. Third parties present on the Sites, such as advertisers, may also place cookies on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We restrict third parties who may place cookies on your browser from having access to any personally identifiable information you have given to us.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Sites may not function properly.

Other than the cookies noted above, we will never download without your explicit permission any applications or other files to your hard drive.

### Information We Collect From You

* * *

While on the Sites, you may provide personal information such as your name, age, gender, address, and email address. Nowhere on the Sites do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

### How We Use Personal Information

* * *

We will use your personal information to contact you and provide you with information that you may request.

We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Sites or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information to allow third parties (including blogs, ecommerce, retailer, or manufacturers) to organize, identify, sort, attribute and publish our content on their public website, in their public marketing materials or for other public or private use by such third parties. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

EXPO may share aggregate statistical information with its partners, suppliers and other third parties. EXPO may also share personal information with a third party including but not limited to first name, last initial, city and state of residence, selected interests, or date of birth but will not include last name, or direct contact information such as email, street address or telephone number. A member may request that such direct contact information be shared, by opting-in to programs or newsletters that may require such information. Unless you tell us not to, we may also use your personal information to contact you about offers or promotions we think you would be interested in. If at any time you would like to stop receiving such information or opt-out of a feature, you can let us know by sending an e-mail stating your preference to [privacy@gen.video](mailto:privacy@gen.video?Subject=). To help us address your request, please specify the feature from which you wish to opt out.

Please note that deletions of your personal information or changes in your preferences may not be effective immediately.

Your personal information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership, assets or the bankruptcy of EXPO. We may also disclose specific information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law or to protect the interests or safety of EXPO or other visitors to the Sites.

Please note that if you give out personal information online in public forums such as on an EXPO message board or on video or profile comments, that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although EXPO strives to protect its users’ privacy, EXPO cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums. You disclose such information at your own risk.

### Email Marketing

* * *

All of our email offerings are “opt-in” programs so you will never receive email from gen.video that you haven’t authorized. We do not sell or rent lists of our users’ email addresses to any third parties.

### Other Sites

* * *

The Sites may contain links to other Web sites, such as retailer or product manufacturer Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or for the privacy policies and practices of other third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

### Our Security Precautions

* * *

The Sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard technology to protect the security of your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Accessing Your Information

* * *

gen.video gives you the opportunity to remove personal information that you have provided to us or change your preferences. If you would like to review or delete any personal information we have retained about you in our database, please send us an email request at [privacy@gen.video](mailto:privacy@gen.video?Subject=). To help us address your request, please specify which information you wish to review or delete. Deleting your information or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from gen.video will delete the data only in our database for purposes of managing future communications from gen.video.
